Preliminary Guide to the Susan Hill Papers, 1976-2003 (bulk 1981-1999) RL.00545
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Susan Hill papers
1976-2003 (bulk 1981-1999)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Hill, Susan
RL.00545
24 Linear Feet
15,972 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted: Box 9 of Accession 2003-0241 is closed to patron use.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Susan Hill Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2003.
Biographical Note
North Carolina native; social worker; activist for reproductive rights; founder and director, National Women's Health Organization (NWHO, an organization of eight clinics serving as a leader in providing abortion services to under-served areas of the United States since 1976). President, National Women's Health Foundation, support foundation to the NWHO.
Collection Overview
Collection consists primarily of newspaper clippings (local, national, and international) pertaining to abortion, the anti-abortion movement, and other women's health issues, kept by staff of the National Women's Health Organization (NWHO) and its regional clinics (WHOs) in Raleigh, N.C.; Columbus, Ga.; Wilmington, Del.; Jackson, Miss.; Fargo, N.D.; Fort Worth, Tex.; Orlando, Fla.; and Milwaukee, Wis. Also contains NWHO legal files, largely pertaining to the NOW (National Organization of Women) v. Scheidler case (1986-2003), and to RICO (the Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act), which plaintiffs in the case applied to the anti-abortion movement. Regional WHO clinics were among the plaintiffs for NOW v. Scheidler, and Hill acted as a key witness. The collection also includes a small number of general office/subject files. Arranged into three categories: Clippings, General Office/Subject Files, and Legal Files. The Clippings were received in chronological groupings, and are thus described in more detail than the General Office/Subject Files and Legal Files, which are less organized.
Accessions (2008-0114 and 2009-0110) consist largely of operational and legal files from the NWHO and its regional clinics, including Raleigh, N.C.; Columbus, Ga.; Delaware; Central Florida; Fargo, N.D.; Fort Wayne, Ind.; and Summit (Milwaukee), Wis. Materials include facilities management files; leases and other real estate information; litigation records and lawsuits between NWHO and anti-abortion groups; police and case reports; statutes about abortion procedures; and NWHO board meeting files.
Accession (2010-0019) consists of audiovisual material: 24 VHS tapes plus 2 DVD copies (master and use) of each tape. Contents include news specials relating to NWHO and the abortion debate; also includes testimony footage, interviews, and other NWHO events.
Legal files; Abortion; Abortion services; Pro-life movement; Women -- Health and hygiene -- United States; Women's health services; Clippings (information artifacts); National Organization for Women -- Trials, litigation, etc.; National Women's Health Organization; Hill, Susan; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; United States. Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act
- Accession (2003-0241)
  - Clippings
    - National WHO and Raleigh WHO (Box 1)
      - 1976-1980 (Box 1)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 1)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 1)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 1)
      - 1988-1990 (Box 2)
      - 1991 (Box 2)
      - 1992 (Box 3)
      - 1993 (Box 3)
      - 1994 (Box 4)
      - 1995 (Box 4)
      - 1997-1999 (Box 4)
    - Columbus WHO
      - 1981-1996 (Box 4)
    - Delaware WHO
      - 1978-1982 (Box 4)
      - 1983-1986 (Box 5)
      - 1986-1990 (Box 5)
      - 1991-1995 (Box 5)
    - Fargo WHO
      - 1981-1985 (Box 5)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 5)
      - 1987-1990 (Box 6)
      - 1991 (Box 6)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 6)
      - 1994-1999 (Box 6)
    - Fort Wayne WHO
      - 1993-1997 (Box 6)
    - Jackson WHO (Box 7)
      - 1994-1997 (Box 7)
    - Orlando (Central Florida) WHO
      - 1977-1981 (Box 7)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 7)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 7)
      - 1986-1999 (Box 7)
    - Summit (Milwaukee) WHO
      - 1990-1998 (Box 7)
      - 1990-1998 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Gunn Clippings, 1993-1995 (Box 8)
    - RICO Case Clippings, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1986-1998 (Box 8)
  - General Office/Subject Files
    - Anti-Abortionists (Box 8)
    - NWHO-RTL-Profiles (Box 8)
    - OSHA and CLIA Related Publications (Box 8)
    - Medicare Provider Manual, 1996 (Box 8)
    - CLOSED materials (Box 9)
  - Legal Files (Box 10-17)
    - NWHO files largely related to RICO and the NOW v. Scheidler case (Box 10-17)
      Scope and Contents note
      Includes Supreme Court documents, briefs, interragatories, motions, exhibits, dispositions, correspondence, research materials, and notes.
- Accessions (2008-0114 and 2009-0110), 22 boxes
  Accessions (2008-0114 and 2009-0110) (9,900 items; 13.2 lin. ft.; dated 1979-1999) consist largely of operational and legal files from the National Women's Health Organization (NWHO) and its regional clinics, including Raleigh, N.C.; Columbus, Ga.; Delaware; Central Florida; Fargo, N.D.; Jackson, Miss.; Fort Wayne, Ind.; and Summit (Milwaukee), Wis. Materials include facilities management files; leases and other real estate information; litigation records and lawsuits between NWHO and anti-abortion groups; police and case reports; statutes about abortion procedures; and NWHO board meeting files.
  - Summit WHO trial materials, 1989 (Box 1)
  - U.S. v. McMillan, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Fort Wayne WHO Operation Rescue correspondence (Box 1)
  - Fargo WHO legal correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 1)
  - Fargo WHO 24-hour consent law, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Nancy Sabot v. Fargo WHO, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Fargo WHO v. FM Women's Help, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Fargo WHO v. Lambs of Christ, 1991-1998 (Box 2)
  - Fargo WHO
    - House Bills 1460 and 1579 (distribution of birth control devices and abortion referrals) (Box 2)
    - Minor's consent statute (Box 2)
    - political correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 2)
  - Jackson WHO
    - PA license rule, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Standards of operation, 1991-1998 (Box 2)
    - Informed consent: information and resources, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Real estate taxes, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
    - Building engineering, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Ambulatory surgical facility application, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Declaration by Susan Hill, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Fargo WHO
    - Son Times publication, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Saving America's Souls: Operation Rescue's Crusade Against Abortion, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackonville, Florida: Operation Rescue, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Jackson WHO (Box 3)
    - Property report, 1991-1994 (Box 3)
    - AMSU correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
    - Informed consent, parental consent, 24-hour informed consent, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
    - Floor plans, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Building suppliers (Box 3)
    - Clinical Laboratory Improvement Amendments (CLIA), 1994-1996 (Box 3)
    - Mississippi application for abortion license, 1999 (Box 3)
    - State legal correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 3)
    - Y&S Realty lease (Box 3)
    - Protective order, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Security systems and information, 1994 (Box 3)
    - Medical equipment, correspondence, scrub sink, etc. (Box 3)
  - Delaware WHO
    - 1984-1989 (Box 3)
    - DWHO v. Richard Wier, Jr., 1977 (Box 3)
    - Parental consent statute (Box 3)
    - Defendant trial dates, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Parade and picketing statute, 1985 (Box 3)
    - Invasion of clinic, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Central Florida WHO v. Operation Rescue, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Legal cases, 1980s (Box 4)
  - Correspondence and evidence for legal cases (Box 4)
  - City of Wilmington v. Louis Johnson and Daniel E. Menefee, 1985 (Box 4)
  - State of Delaware v. David M. Hoch, Doris Mantyla, et al., Vol. A, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Altamonte Surgicenter, Ltd., 1980s (Box 4)
  - National WHO meeting notes, 1999-2001 (Box 4)
  - Susan Hill deposition transcripts, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Legal cases (Box 5)
  - Dr. Warren Hern files (Box 5)
  - Fargo WHO real estate appraisal (Box 5)
  - Central Florida WHO blueprints (Box 5)
  - Delaware police reports (Box 5)
  - Central Florida WHO trial materials, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Central Florida WHO insurance policies, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  - Pro-choice buttons (Box 5)
  - Summit WHO (Box 6)
    - 24-hour consent (Box 6)
    - Letters from tenants at Jefferson Building, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Confidentiality statute (Box 6)
    - Nursing statute (Box 6)
    - Right to Life (Box 6)
    - Picketing statute (Box 6)
    - Patient health care records (Box 6)
  - Gloria Jean Jackson v. Central Florida WHO (Box 6)
  - Real estate, Wisconsin (Box 6)
  - Summit WHO
    - New building correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Parental notification correspondence, 1997 (Box 6)
  - National Political RTL: Field Manual for Militia (Box 6)
  - National WHO
    - Anti-abortion antics, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Feminist majority, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - ACLU, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Right to Lifers: Paul Hill, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Medical abortion, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Fargo WHO
    - Motion of Krueger, Krueger-related correspondence, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Lease, 1998 (Box 6)
  - National WHO
    - Anti-stalking laws, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Army of God, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Reports: anti-abortion, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Staff, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Reproductive Rights Issues Manual, NARAL, 1990 (Box 6)
    - The Political Report, NARAL, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Delaware WHO
    - Zoning code, New Castle county, 1985 (Box 6)
    - State v. Van Ness Johnson, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Milwaukee Medical Service v. Pastors' Emergency League (Box 6)
    - State of Delaware v. Roach, et al., 1994 (Box 6)
    - Mitch Road property (Box 6)
    - Medical clinic protocol (Box 6)
  - Delaware WHO (Box 7)
    - 1020 W. 18th St. contract and miscellaneous correspondence, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Building plans for 2123 W. Newport Pike, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Business license, 1997 (Box 7)
    - CLIA correspondence, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Parental, 24-hour consent law, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Rules and regulations for AMSU Central, 1988 (Box 7)
    - DEA inspection, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Delaware State Senate, 1981-1984 (Box 7)
    - Flood line determination: Red Clay Creek II (Box 7)
    - Invoices for new building, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Sign ordinance, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Child abuse statute, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Confidentiality statute, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Central Florida WHO
    - Clinic licensing and laws, 1981-1983 (Box 7)
    - DEA correspondence, 1998 (Box 7)
    - 1700 Colonial Dr., 1982 (Box 7)
    - Confidentiality statute (Box 7)
    - Central Florida WHO v. City of Orlando, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Fort Wayne WHO consent forms, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Central Florida WHO
    - Lease, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Property taxes, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Letter to state by Carol Reed, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1990 (Box 7)
    - Sewer service policy, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Dr. Snydle affidavit (Box 7)
    - Florida laboratory rules, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Partial birth abortion ban, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Regulation cases, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Statutes, spouse notification, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Burglary trespass statutes, 1983 (Box 7)
    - State inspections, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Noise ordinance statute (Box 7)
    - Parental consent statute, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Picketing statute, 1983 (Box 7)
    - South St. property, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Zoning, 1982 (Box 7)
    - John Jones, MD v. James Smith, Aty, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Building estimates, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Real estate, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Florida statutes, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Abortion statutes, 1983 (Box 8)
    - NFARAL, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Medical files
      - Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 8)
      - Medicaid correspondence, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Chart forms, 1990 (Box 8)
      - General anesthesia protocol (Box 8)
      - Infection control committee meeting reports, 1991 (Box 8)
      - Licensed HMOs in Florida, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
      - Mid-trimester protocol, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 8)
      - State board licensure, 1996 (Box 8)
      - Nitrous oxide, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence
      - Miscellaneous, 1992-1998 (Box 8)
      - Nowell's furniture (Box 8)
      - Open house (includes photographs), 1992 (Box 8)
      - Outgoing, 1998 (Box 8)
      - Yellow Pages (Box 9)
      - Ultrasound, 1991 (Box 9)
      - Public relations, 1997-1999 (Box 9)
      - Financial statement of assets and liabilities, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
      - Inventory, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Insurance (Box 9)
      - Armed service pick-up, 1987 (Box 9)
      - Competition reports, 1985-1988 (Box 9)
      - Incoming (includes photographs) (Box 9)
      - Bio-hazard waste, 1992 (Box 9)
      - Bomb evacuation plan (Box 9)
      - Incoming, 1995-1997 (Box 9)
      - Florida Senate survey, 1989 (Box 9)
      - Occupational license, 1998 (Box 9)
      - Patient records statute, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Orlando Women's Center, 1996 (Box 9)
      - Insurance coverage, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Clippings (photocopies) (Box 9)
  - National legal class action (Box 9)
  - Fort Wayne WHO Case 1368, 1979-1990 (Box 9)
  - General litigation (Box 9)
  - Delaware WHO abortion law, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Fort Wayne WHO
    - Fort Wayne WHO and Klopfer v. Brane, Brown, Brown, et al., 1990 (Box 9)
    - Case 1368 patient's record (Box 9)
    - Articles: Bryan Brown information (Box 10)
    - Fire, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Fort Wayne WHO v. Wendall Brane (Box 10)
    - RICO case, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Fort Wayne WHO v. Scott Newman, 1998 (Box 10)
    - FACE case, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Clinic setup, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
    - Lease, 1979-1988 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - Broadview Lumber v. Y&S Management (Box 10)
    - Correspondence: Joan Uebelhoer, 1989 (Box 10)
    - Parental notification statute, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Intrauterine Devices and Their Complications, 1979 (Box 10)
  - ACLU Legal Dockets, 1986, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Fargo WHO Joe Scheidler (Box 11)
  - Mary Voors v. National WHO (Box 11)
  - Supreme Court appeal (Akron/VA) (Box 11)
  - National WHO
    - General reports (Box 11)
    - Sharp police response, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Bomb threat protocol, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Columbus WHO: minors and parental consent statute, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Senate bill 873, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Raleigh WHO
    - Consent for minors, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Rosie J. v. NC Department of Human Resources, 1996 (Box 11)
    - Raleigh WHO v. Mass Mutual, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Fire threat, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 2008 (Folder 1 includes color code for labelling folders) (Box 12)
    - NARAL (Box 12)
    - NC Providers meeting, February 1992 (Box 12)
    - Planned Parenthood of NC Bond (Box 12)
    - RTL demonstration, October 1988 (Box 12)
    - Save-A-Baby correspondence, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Security/escort correspondence (Box 12)
    - Political correspondence, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Operation Rescue, 1988-1992 (Box 12)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Political correspondence, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Jesse Helms, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Letters from tenants, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Operation Rescue: Medical care of Durham v. Marsha Green (Box 12)
  - Fort Wayne WHO asset/judgment recovery, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Milwaukee rules, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Fargo WHO
    - Sue Wicklund, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Laws/legal overview, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Indiana injunction, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Yachnowitz v. Hill, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Joseph Scheidler case, 1999 (Box 13)
  - RICHO, 1998 (Box 13)
  - EEOC complaints, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Jackson, Miss. regulations, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Adelman and Hynes malpractice (Box 13)
  - Jackson medicaid case, 2000 (Box 13)
  - National WHO - Jackson, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Fargo WHO correspondence, appraisal, and real estate (Box 13)
  - Operation Rescue, 1988-1994 (Box 13)
  - Summit WHO (Box 14)
    - Karlin, Planned Parenthood, Prohaska, and Christiansen v. Fouse and Doyle, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Notice of intent to revoke certificate of authority, 1986 (Box 14)
    - State requirements for technicians, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Hospital clinic definition, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Report of fetal disposal, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Regulation cases, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Parental notification (Box 14)
    - McCann letters to DA, 1998 (Box 14)
    - Floor plans (Box 14)
    - Merger, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Family health plan cooperative contract (Box 14)
    - Lease: 530 Water St., 1989 (Box 14)
    - Wisconsin state law Act 56, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Wisconsin v. Missionaries (Scheidler), 1989-1990 (Box 14)
    - New building plans (Box 14)
    - Abortion statute, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Partnership agreement, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Security, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Planned Parenthood evaluation, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Insurance, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Protocols, MD resumes, standing orders equipment (Box 15)
    - Anti-abortion activities, 1985-1997 (Box 15)
    - Zoning Out Abortion article, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1999 (Box 15)
    - Operation Rescue arrest, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Harassment of Dr. Duncan, 1998 (Box 15)
  - Columbus WHO picketing statute (Box 15)
  - Raleigh WHO
    - Certificate of incorporation, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Haworth properties (Box 15)
    - Rules and regulations for abortion clinics, 1994 (Box 15)
    - New building plans, 1991 (Box 16)
    - Lease (Box 16)
    - Medical assistance program, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Manning v. State: legal minor consent, 1996 (Box 16)
    - Abortion clinic certification, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Picketing statute, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Consent law (Box 16)
    - Licensing (Box 16)
  - Fargo WHO
    - Anti-abortion publications and protests, 1992 (Box 16)
    - L.I.F.E. coalition (Box 16)
    - Life advocate (Box 16)
    - Planned Parenthood mailing, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Political campaigns, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Columbus WHO
    - Georgians for Choice, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Georgia abortion provider, 1993-1997 (Box 17)
  - Operation Rescue, 1988-1994 (Box 17)
  - Fort Wayne WHO
    - Case 1368, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Nurses Concerned for Life v. National WHO, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 17)
    - 24-hour waiting period, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Corporate minutes, 1988 (Box 17)
    - RICO, 1990 (Box 17)
  - National WHO Board meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - Fargo WHO (Box 19)
    - David Larson v. Fargo WHO, 1996 (Box 19)
    - George Miks, MD v. Allen Olson, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Fargo WHO v. Larson (Box 19)
    - North Dakota v. Family SVC (Box 19)
    - Fargo WHO v. Lambs of Christ (Box 19)
    - Fargo WHO v. David Pence, 1990 (Box 19)
  - Fort Wayne WHO (Box 20)
    - Nurses Concerned for Life, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
    - RICO (Box 20)
    - Parental consent, 1984 (Box 20)
    - Certificate of incorporation, 1977 (Box 20)
    - Abortion statute (Box 20)
    - Confidentiality statute (Box 20)
    - Sex abuse law, 1987 (Box 20)
    - Fetal disposition bills (Box 20)
    - Picketing statutes (Box 20)
  - Fargo WHO (Box 21)
    - Legal cases (Box 21)
      Includes David Pence and Lambs of Christ (1992), George Skinner (1991), North Dakota Department of Human Resources (1995), Timothy Lindgren (1995), Prairie Design (1994).
    - Planned Parenthood v. Minnesota (fetal disposal), 1990 (Box 21)
    - Larson v. City of Fargo (residential picketing), 1993 (Box 21)
    - Fargo WHO v. State of N.D. (24-hour consent law), 1993 (Box 21)
    - Nancy Sabot v. Fargo WHO, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Certificate of incorporation, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Picketing and 24-hour notice of protests, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Patient confidentiality (Box 22)
    - Cases
      - Fargo WHO v. Ed. Schafer (governor of North Dakota), 1993 (Box 22)
      - Fargo WHO v. Terry Carlson, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Fargo WHO v. Larson (Box 22)
      - Tamara Green v. Fargo WHO, 1991 (Box 22)
- Accession (2010-0019), 2 boxes
  Accession (2010-0019) (72 items; 1.2 lin. ft.) contains audiovisual materials: 24 VHS tapes plus 2 DVD copies (master and use) of each tape. Contents include news specials relating to NWHO and the abortion debate; also includes testimony footage, interviews, and other NWHO events.
  - Videotapes (originals) (Box 1)
    - Susan Hill, Fort Wayne, 1989 Apr. 26 (Box 1)
    - FWWHO, 1989 June 10 (Box 1)
    - Rescue PPFA Summary, Ft. Worth, Ind., 1989 Apr. 21 (2 copies) (Box 1)
    - Jane's Tape: Abortion Stories (Box 1)
    - 20/20: Abortion Fargo Geraldo, 1985 Jan. (Box 1)
    - Donahue: Dr. David Gunn (Box 1)
    - Congressional testimony, 1992 Apr. (Box 1)
    - Congressional testimony, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Hill testimony on Clinic Blockade (Box 1)
    - Freedom Forum Freedom Speaks: Abortion 1994 Oct. 3 (Box 1)
    - Viewer call-in program, 1994 Sept. 22 (Box 1)
    - Pro-life demonstration: Joe Scheidler, 1987 Feb. 27 (Box 1)
    - Freedom Forum Freedom Speaks, 1994 Oct. 3 (Box 1)
    - The Shirley Show: Killing Abortion Doctors (Box 1)
    - Ft. Wayne, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Picket, Fargo Women's Health, 1987 Nov. 13 (Box 1)
    - Picket, 1992 May (Box 1)
    - Access Denied, 1991 (Box 1)
    - FWWHO Clinic, 1989 May (Box 1)
  - Videotapes (originals) (Box 2)
    - Tractorman newscast (Fox 22), David Betts (Box 2)
    - Susan Hill home video: childhood in Durham, N.C. (Box 2)
    - Conspiracy tapes: 60 Minutes Fargo with Geraldo (Box 2)
    - Abortion: For Survival (Box 2)
  - DVD masters of all 24 tapes (Box 2)
  - DVD use copies of all 24 tapes (Box 2)